Starve Acre is a horror, drama, fantasy film directed by Daniel Kokotajlo.
When their son starts acting strangely, a couple unwittingly allow dark and sinister forces into
their home, awakening a long-dormant ancient evil rooted deep in the countryside.
Richard, played by Matt Smith.
Juliette, played by Morfydd Clark.
Owen, played by Arthur Shaw.
Harrie, played by Erin Richards.
Gordon, played by Sean Gilder.
Mrs. Forde, played by Melanie Kilburn.
Starve Acre is a 2023 British folk horror film written and directed by Daniel
Kokotajlo, based upon the 2019 novel of the same name by Andrew Michael Hurley.
The film stars Matt Smith and Morfydd Clark.
Starve Acre had its world premiere at the BFI London Film Festival on 12 October
2023, and was released in the United Kingdom on 6 September 2024.
The film explores themes of small town, based on novel or
book, 1970s, archaeologist, folk horror.
The tone is dark and thought_provoking and emotional.